Open the project file material, draw a curve, paste the picture, paste it, add a curve and an eye for it.
Select the curve tool in the 3D tool bar.
In the 2D window, click on the curve position, left-click, add a curve.
The 3D window can be operated in the same way.
Left-click the long-press curve tool, click on the eye tool, add an eye on the other side of the collar.
In the 3D tool bar, click on the curve tool.
In the 2D or 3D window, click on the curve, then click on the eye.
When there is such a small lock icon on the curve in the 3D window, the 2D window is the curve arrow pointing to the eye, which means it is in harmony.
If you want to cancel the harmony, use the curve tool to left-click on the curve or the eye.
The curve and the eye can be solved.
Thank you for your attention.
Next, we will change the size and properties of the button and button eye.
In the object window, select the button.
In the property editor, you can enter the name and product number of the button.
Click on the triangle on the right side of the sample.
You can change it to another button shape.
The four-hole button can also be adjusted to the line type.
From cross to parallel or square.
Here, the sample is selected as 2, Shank, Button, 04.
Under the specifications, the width, thickness and weight of the button and button can be changed.
Under the width, the button and eye can be used in conjunction with each other.
In this way, the button and eye specifications corresponding to it will also be changed in conjunction.
Note that the function must be used in the state of button and button eye combination.
Use the button and eye combination.
Adjust the button and eye width, thickness and weight.
Next, change the type and color of the button and eye material.
Then, change the type, material type and color of the button and eye.
Switch to the tool to select the moving button and eye.
In the 2D window or 3D window, select the button and eye.
You can move its position.
In the property editor, you can adjust the angle of the button and the length of the line.
Next is the conflict.
The default conflict of the button and the eye is opened.
In this way, there is a collision relationship between the button and the plate when the model is simulated.
The button and the eye can be fully simulated on the surface of the plate.
In some specific cases, if the button and the plate are not simulated, the collision can be closed.
Measure the position of 2D.
The default is closed.
Open it and show the end point of the button and eye at the 2D window.
The upper and lower left and right, according to the distance of the outer line of the plate, select the middle eye.
In the property editor, you can adjust the angle of the eye.
Adjust the eye to the level position.
According to the distance of this axis, you can adjust the vertical distance between the eye and the plate on the plane.
You can also adjust the position of the line.
You can see that the position of the adjustment button and button line is located to the left or to the right or to the middle.
It can also show the 2D measurement position.
Next, add the button and the eye at the door.
Add one by one.
There is a faster way to add.
Select the button and button tool.
In the first button and button position at the door, click.
Add a button and button.
Switch to the option to move the button and button tool.
Select this button and button.
Select copy.
Then click the button again.
Select paste.
There is a button and button on the mouse.
And move with the mouse.
In the second button and button position on the plate, click again.
A window will pop up.
Enter the number of buttons.
After the button is confirmed, the button will be added.
Select the button and button.
Right-click the button.
Select to copy the eye to the symmetrical plate.
The eye is added.
Next, I will explain the meaning of other options in the menu after right-clicking the button and button.
Use the option to move the button and button tool.
Right-click the button and button in the 3D or 2D window.
Then click the button and button tool and select the menu.
Select Re burnt 3D position.
The button can be re-bnt to the simulation position.
You can paste to one button and multiple buttons.
You can also select and copy after single button.
Paste multiple buttons at once.
The operation method is the same as the above installation.
You can also delete selected buttons.
Duplicate to symmetrical edit board.
to the symmetrical panel.
Select the button to be converted into a buttonhole,
and the button to be converted into a buttonhole.
You can also reverse activate and freeze the buttonhole.
Select the layer to be sewn.
You can set the layer to be sewn
under the multi-layer panel.
The flip is used to change the button
on the front or back of the fabric.
Click on the button on the buttonhole
to select the buttonhole.
The selected menu options are similar to the buttonhole.
Switch to the buttonhole tool.
Select the buttonhole,
and click on the button after the arrow points to the corresponding buttonhole.
Combine the buttonhole and buttonhole.
After the simulation is stable,
turn off the simulation.
Select the buttonhole or buttonhole in the object window.
The attribute editor
will be saved in the object window.
The current buttonhole and buttonhole
will be saved as btn files.
When needed,
drag the buttonhole from the object window
to the object window.
Or select the default buttonhole
in the object window.
Click on the button in the attribute editor
to open the buttonhole.